What time do you start work?
你什么时候开始工作呢？
Do you prefer a leisurely start to the day, or are you an early bird who likes to get going at the crack of dawn?
你是喜欢悠闲地开始新的一天，还是说你是个早起的人，喜欢在破晓时分就开始忙碌呢？
At one computer programming company in the US you have no such choice.
在美国的一家计算机编程公司，你没有这样的选择。
Work begins at the same oddly specific time every day: 9.06am.
每天的工作都在一个奇怪的特定时间开始：上午9点06分。
In contrast to a more conventional 9am kick-off, employees in Pivotal Software's 20 offices around the globe have to be at work and ready to go precisely six minutes later.
与更传统的上午9点开始工作不同，Pivotal Software公司在全球的20个办公室的员工必须在9点整过6分钟后，准时到岗并做好工作准备。
At that time a cowbell is rung and employees gather for a brief stand-up meeting.
在那个时候，会敲响牛铃，员工们聚在一起开一个简短的站立会议。
After that it's nose to the grindstone, with no other meetings or distractions throughout the working day.
之后大家就开始埋头苦干，在整个工作日里没有其他会议或者干扰。
They steam on through until 6pm sharp, at which point everybody downs tools.
他们一直忙碌到下午6点整，到那个时候，所有人都停止工作。
So what's the reason behind this quirky timekeeping?
那么，这种古怪的计时方式背后的原因是什么呢？
Company CEO Rob Mee explains it's about making his team of computer programmers as efficient as possible.
公司首席执行官罗布·米解释说，这是为了让他的计算机程序员团队尽可能高效。
"I realised that programmers, if left to their own devices, may roll in at 10am," he says.
“我意识到，如果让程序员们自行其是，他们可能会在上午10点才到公司。”
"We thought that if we made it 9am, developers psyching themselves up for the day would think, 'well if it is 9am I'll be late.'"
他说，“我们认为，如果规定9点上班，那些为新一天做准备的开发人员会想，‘嗯，如果已经9点了，那我就迟到了。’”
He needed a little more leeway, but a starting time of 9.05am on the nose felt too rigidly precise — whereas 9.06am seemed “fun”.
他需要多一点回旋余地，但正正好好9点05分这个时间点感觉太严格地精确了——而9点06分似乎“更有趣”。
Mr Mee was also thinking of their stomachs.
米先生也考虑到了员工的胃。
Lazier programmers who turned up around 10am would also often have missed breakfast.
那些比较懒、大约上午10点出现在公司的程序员常常也会错过早餐。
This meant they would be hungry by 11am and take an early lunch, leaving them with an interminably long working afternoon ahead.
这就意味着他们在上午11点就会饿，然后提前吃午饭，这样他们接下来的下午工作时间就会无限地漫长。
So he decided to provide breakfast as an extra incentive to get in to the office on time.
所以他决定提供早餐，作为让员工准时到达办公室的额外激励措施。
The company's approach to punctuality may seem nerdy, but Pivotal Software is in fact a highly successful company, valued at 20bn RMB.
该公司对守时的做法可能看起来有点书呆子气，但Pivotal Software实际上是一家非常成功的公司，估值200亿元人民币。
And Pivotal is not alone: Silicon Valley has long been associated with an alternative working culture.
而且Pivotal并非个例：硅谷长期以来一直与一种非传统的工作文化联系在一起。
Google has 'nap pods' and meditation classes, while Netflix offers a year's paid parental leave.
谷歌有“午睡舱”和冥想课程，而网飞公司提供一年的带薪育儿假。